Kobato. 20 TL
“…Travelers.”
9:14 eyecatch}
valentine’s Party
Next Episode
“…The Footsteps of Spring.”
Anyway, don’t worry about it.
Okay.
Kobato.
Y-Yes?
No matter how thick-headed you are,
you’ll eventually catch a cold with the window open.
But I’m…
I’m freezing, got it?!
I’m sorry!
It really is quite cold.
Yeah, we just entered February.
Now that I think about it it, at the convenience store,
there were a lot of magazines with chocolate on the covers.
Maybe eating chocolate makes people feel warmer!
That’s because Valentine’s Day is coming up.
Valentine’s Day?
Fujimoto-san!
February 14th is Valentine’s Day, right?
What about it?
Should we hold a Valentine’s party at Yomogi Preschool?
Why at a preschool?
You don’t hold them in preschools?
They happen, but in Japan, it’s the day when you give out chocolates, right?
Yes!
That’s what it said in a book!
So even in a preschool…
The girls give them to guys, right?
It’s the day when girls give chocolate to guys they like.
That’s what Valentine’s Day is about?
Well, the opposite has been happening lately, too.
But anyway, you really don’t know anything, do you?
The one I like…
What?
Why not try a Valentine’s party?
Sayaka-sensei… seems to have something on her mind again.
She’s hurting a lot, but she’s trying not to show it.
I was thinking we could cheer her up, at least a little, on Valentine’s Day.
We can’t, though.
The preschool doesn’t have the money to do something like that right now.
It’s all right!
Ch-Chiroru can share some ingredients with us, I think.
If we go in the morning and ask them,
as long as we work for the chocolate we make, it should be fine!
Calm down a bit.
Y-Yes…
In other words, you make a deal to help out at the Chiroru cake bakery
in return for ingredients the preschool can use to make chocolates, right?
Right, right.
Um, did I do anything wrong?
I’ve got a lot of work piled up,
so helping out at Chiroru might be difficult…
I’ve got construction work at midnight too…
Only I need to help!
The manager said that I just need to help out
every day after Yomogi Preschool is over until Valentine’s Day!
But…
It’s all right!
For Valentine’s Day…
…I’ll do my best!
Fight! Hiya! Hiya!
Then, good luck.
Kobato-chan wants to celebrate Valentine’s Day here?
Yeah.
She sure is such a sweet girl.
Thanks for waiting!
Thank you.
Thank you for coming!
Good work.
Good work!
I can still work more!
I’d like that, but…
It’s closing time already.
It’s already that late?
Um, um… is there anything else I can help with?
Valentine’s Day is still two days away.
You’ve worked plenty.
Then, would you put away the sign out front?
Yes! I’ll go do that!
That hurt!
Looks like we fell in a weird way again.
We didn’t land in the ocean or
something this time, so isn’t it better?
We almost died that time!
Ioryogi-san?
A girl!
It’s a world with humans!
Hey!
We don’t know if white meatbun-looking things speak here!
Ioryogi-san?
Um… this person’s called Kurogane-san.
And I’m Fay.
And this is Syaoran-kun.
And this is…
Huh?
Wh-What is it?
Well…
I see!
Mokona, it’s okay to talk.
This girl isn’t surprised.
Yes!
After all, Ioryogi-san’s also a talking stuffed animal!
Ioryogi-san?
Kobato, you!
How long are you going to loiter?!
The manager’s worried about you-
Ioryogi-san!
So that’s Ioryogi-san!
I’m Mokona. Nice to meet you!
You little…!
You’re from that amusement park!
You’re traveling?
Yeah.
All four of you?
Three plus one Mokona!
One Mokona?
That’s how you count off Mokonas!
So that means, Ioryogi-san would be one Ioryogi-san!
No!
That’s not what it means!
It’s true… Kuro-sama and
Ioryogi-san do sound similar.
No, we don't!
They do.
They really do.
The Kurogane in this world is tiny and blue!
Shut up, you white meatbun!
You stupid little…
Then, you came here for a journey?
That’s right.
Quit running, you little punk!
I read about it in a book. You go to
all sorts of places when on a journey.
Have you already decided where you’re going?
No… not yet.
It’d be nice if we had a place to stay.
But…
We don’t have any money from this world.
You don’t have money?
The money we have now
probably wouldn’t be of use here.
That sounds like a problem.
Well, we don’t have any girls,
so camping out should be fine.
Mokona’s a girl though.
How can you tell the gender?
The color?
The cuteness!
Um, if you’re looking…
Would you like to stay at my place?
I knew it!
B-But…
It’s all right!
I have a room!
But I only have one futon…
But, but, if you all gather around to sleep…
But you’re kind of big…
Oh! If we use both the top and bottom futons separately…
If you only have one futon, do you live by yourself?
No, I’m with Ioryogi-san!
Then we really shouldn’t…
It’s really all right!
Let’s stay.
Um…
I’m Hanato Kobato!
Thanks, Kobato-chan.
Hey, you guys…
Whatever happens, Ioryogi-san will protect you, right?
Hey…
Now then, let’s go to Kobato-chan’s place!
Go!
Let’s head out.
Is this really okay?
He must have thought this
through if that’s his decision.
Kuro-tan.
Why are you frowning?
Oh, I mixed up the two of you!
Or so I thought…
That idiot probably didn’t think anything through!
I’m late!
I’ve got the day off from the preschool,
but I still needed to be at Chiroru’s in the morning!
We kept trying to wake you up though.
Kobato’s a heavy sleeper.
You’re no different no matter how many people are in the room.
Sorry!
Um… I’ll be heading out, but feel free to stay in my room!
Kobato-chan, you’re going to a cake bakery, right?
Yes, to help out!
Um… you’re going to get ingredients for Valentine’s Day chocolates, right?
Yes.
Then we’ll help out too.
That sounds nice!
It’ll be our thanks for letting us stay here!
For the store, let’s see…
Syaoran-kun, would you go with her?
You’re good with food.
I don’t think Kuro-sama would be suited for a cake bakery…
I wouldn’t want to anyway.
Kuro-tan and I will find some work somewhere else.
To gather some funds.
Mokona…
I’ll be with Ioryogi-san!
Why?
I feel friendly today!
Well, I don’t!
That’s settled then.
Everyone, do your best!
Yeah!
Ioryogi-san, do your best, too!
Teamwork between friends!
I’m not your friend!
But you must be jealous of Mokona’s cuteness!
Why would I be?!
Yumi-chan, who’s that guy?
Oh, Kobato-chan’s acquaintance.
Mokona’s pretty good at
pretending to be a stuffed animal.
Don’t talk!
Amazing!
Shaoran-san, you’re really handy!
It’s easy once you’re used to it.
I’ve practiced so much, but I can’t do it so smoothly…
Don’t try to put it all in at once, but slowly, like this…
Slowly…
I did it!
Don’t sing either!
Shaoran-san, have you and the others always been traveling?
Yeah.
But we don’t have a destination.
Is that so?
The purpose of it is pretty much to keep traveling.
Um… so you don’t know where you’re going next?
It’s difficult to figure that out.
We don’t even know how long
we can spend in any single place.
But…
There’s someone waiting for me.
Someone waiting for you?
I don’t know when I’ll return, but she’s back there waiting for me.
I…
…also have a place I want to go to.
I want to go there no matter what.
Is that because you have a reason for going there?
Or is it because you want to meet someone there?
Someone… I want to meet?
The one I want to meet…
We’ve done a lot of work!
All you did was sit!
Yes, working as a decoration!
What’s with that?!
Welcome back!
How was the cake bakery?
We’re back!
Syaoran-san was very handy, and the manager complimented him a lot!
Oh, no…
Although they said our clothes were unusual.
Oh, our clothes.
We had a lot of problems too.
Everyone asked if we were cosplaying.
It got complicated because you kept saying,
“Does this count as cosplay in this world?”
Here, for you.
It’s one envelope for one day, so it’s not much, but…
But is it really okay?
Yeah, we’ll be happy if you take it.
It’s our thanks for letting us stay.
Thank you!
I’ll use it to help Yomogi Preschool!
Already?
What’s wrong?
When this earpiece glows,
we have to go to the next world.
Thanks for letting us stay.
It was only one night, but it was fun!
Sorry for the trouble.
Oh, no, sorry I couldn’t be of more help.
Hey, is Kobato-chan…
…right?
It seems she’s rather insecure.
That’s a really majestic light!
Isn’t it? Mokona really likes it!
As someone from another world, you can only watch over her…
…and that goes for us too.
Be careful.
I know that even without you telling me.
I want one! I really want one!
I hope you can go to that place.
Thank you.
Who were they?
They were from another world.
The human world isn’t the only one around, after all.
The Celestial World, the Nether World, the Spirit World…
There might be a lot of others, too.
I hope…
…that their next world will be where
Syaoran-san can meet the one waiting for him.
Everyone looks like they’re having fun.
Yeah.
Kobato-chan really worked hard.
Well… yes.
Kobato-chan, that looks weird.
What is it?
What is it supposed to be?
It’s supposed to be a star…
You mean it’s not a starfish?
It looks like a starfish?!
Not just chocolate, but she gave us money too.
And she brought wrappings and
cards with the chocolate as well.
I hope Kobato-chan isn’t pushing herself too much.
Hey, hey. Yoshio-kun, who are you giving your chocolate to?
My mom and dad. And my little sister!
I’ll give mine to my mom…
and Kobato-chan, if you want.
Thank you!
You’ve gotta give your best Valentine’s chocolate
to the one you like the most, after all.
Kobato-chan, who are you going to give your best to?
Me?
That Kobato… you’re making some for me too, right?
What is it?
Kobato…
You really…
…don’t have any time left.